// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q012: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Given the recent rise in problems with social networking services, it has become ------ important to properly disclose information.',
      choices: ['increasing', 'increase', 'increasingly', 'increased'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['increasingly'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q111',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Choi ------ the quality improvement team at the plant for the past two years.',
      choices: ['will oversee', 'has been overseen', 'oversees', 'has overseen'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['has overseen'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q112',
    },
    {
      question: '------ approval from the immediate supervisor is required for any business travel involving an overnight stay.',
      choices: ['Renowned', 'Prior', 'Confident', 'Valuable'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Prior'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q113',
    },
    {
      question: 'You can view your credit card statement and points earned by logging into ------ account.',
      choices: ['your', 'yours', 'yourself', 'you'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['your'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q114',
    },
    {
      question: 'The upcoming walking tour is open to everyone, ------ age, and those who wish to participate should register on the tour website.',
      choices: ['subsequent to', 'in keeping with', 'in place of', 'regardless of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['regardless of'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q115',
    },
    {
      question: 'Reymond Elevator Group asks that elevators ------ at least once every two months.',
      choices: ['inspect', 'are inspected', 'will inspect', 'be inspected'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['be inspected'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q116',
    },
    {
      question: 'Before ------ for a mortgage, you should consider the loan terms of several banks.',
      choices: ['have applied', 'apply', 'will be applied', 'applying'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['applying'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q117',
    },
    {
      question: '------ change your booked bus, please contact the reservation center phone number listed on the back of your ticket.',
      choices: ['For', 'Concerning', 'To', 'Despite'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['To'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q118',
    },
    {
      question: 'The introduction of practical robots is ------ anticipated to make up for labor shortages in the nursing care industry.',
      choices: ['highest', 'high', 'highly', 'higher'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['highly'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q119',
    },
    {
      question: 'Some economic experts are ------ that wheat prices will rise next year, affecting household budgets.',
      choices: ['proceeding', 'predicting', 'approaching', 'focusing'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['predicting'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題111-120/#q120',
    },
  ],
}